As you saw in the previous mini blog, we
came here for a newborn photoshoot.
He came and cut off my nose.  Because at
other times, if I fed him a little, he
would sleep for three hours straight.  And it's been two or three hours since I arrived here.
He does
n't even want to sleep.  Everyone was exhausted when they tried to put him to sleep.
So here we
ordered a pizza from Pampa.  I think
he was having a little trouble sleeping in his new place.
Finally, after two hours of trying,
he was able to get some sleep.
Because if he wants to click good pictures,
he must sleep.  And after he fell asleep,
he was being changed into a new outfit
and placed in a new background.
What more can I tell you about how cute she looked?
I'm slowly posting her beautiful pictures on
Instagram.  And
Suchandadi handled the situation very efficiently.
And you know,
I really liked the background of Harry Potter.
I thought it could only be done if it was a boy.
But he didn't say there were separate dresses for girls.
Be sure to let me know in the comments how my poppy looks in the Harmonic Drencher costume.
The photo of the poster alone was not taken.
We also had some family portraits
taken with him.  Obik's only hope was that he would be able to
see them when he grew up.  So we will not only keep them in soft
copies but also in albums.  It was a very
fun day.  And many pictures have been
clicked.  I will post everything slowly.
You stay tuned.